A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 8, Accession 8 FA1190
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges - General, 1993-2014; 2
  - American Teachers - Dyson, William (1998-1999), 1998-2004; Still Images: 6 4x6 color prints (Box 54, Folder 491)
    Includes images of party for Dyson, students, China.
  - American Teachers - Elliott, Richard C., and Carol M. Elliott (1999-2000) (Box 55, Folder 492)
  - American Teachers - Escobar Pocaterra, Jorge (2012-2013), Still Image: 2 color headshots (2x2) (Box 55, Folder 493)
    Includes passport photos.
  - American Teachers - Fazzolara, Adrienne (2001-2002), 2001-2009 (Box 55, Folder 494)
  - American Teachers - Fox, Karen (1996-1997), 1996-2004; Still Images: 7 color prints (3x5 - 4x6) (Box 55, Folder 495)
    Includes snapshots mainly of orientation programs and teacher reunions.
  - American Teachers - Fray, Christopher (1998-1999), 1998-2010; Still Images: 21 color prints (3x5; one 4x6) (Box 55, Folder 496-497)
    Includes images of students and teachers, Halloween party.
  - American Teachers - Frontiera, Aaron (2003-2004), and Marlo Engler (2004-2005), 2002-2004 (Box 55, Folder 498)
    The 2003 cohort did not travel until 2004-2005 because of the SARS epidemic.
  - American Teachers - Garcia, Iraise (2011-2012) (Box 55, Folder 499)
  - American Teachers - Gouck, Maura (1998-1999), Still Images: 5 4x6 color prints (Box 55, Folder 500)
  - American Teachers - Happel, Tracie (2009-2010) (Box 55, Folder 501)
  - American Teachers - Harmeling, Loanne (2007-2008) (Box 55, Folder 502)
  - American Teachers - Horrigan, John (2000-2001), 2000-2004 (Box 55, Folder 503)
  - American Teachers - James, Kristina (2003-2004) (Box 55, Folder 504)
  - American Teachers - Jackson, Maureen (formerly Maureen Turley) (1996-1997), 1996-2004 (Box 56, Folder 505-506)
  - American Teachers - Joseph, Lizabeth (1999-2000), 1999-2005 (Box 56, Folder 507)
  - American Teachers - Kelly, Susan (2007-2008) (Box 56, Folder 508)
  - American Teachers - Krueger, David (1999-2000), 1999-2004; Still Images: Eleven 4x6 color prints mounted on paper; one 8x10 color print (Box 56, Folder 509)
    Includes booklet of images of Krueger and his students in Milwaukee.
  - American Teachers - Levin, Karen (1996-2006), 1996-1997; Still Images: color prints: 4 4x6, 1 3x5, and 1 polaroid. (Box 56, Folder 510-512)
    Includes snapshotsfrom banquet, display board on China, and Chinese exchange teachers.
  - American Teachers - Lindberg, Stephen (1996-1997), 1996-2004; Still Images: 4 color prints (3x5 - 4x6) (Box 57, Folder 513)
    Includes images of Thanksgiving with Chinese exchange teachers.
  - American Teachers - Maddison, Saige (2013-2014) (Box 57, Folder 514)
  - American Teachers - Magboo, Virginia (1998-1999), 1998-2006; Still images: 11 3x5 color prints (Box 57, Folder 515)
    Includes 11 snapshots of Virginia and others in China.
  - American Teachers - Martin, John F. (1996-1998), 1996-2004; Still Images: ca. 15 color prints (3x5 - 4x6) (Box 57, Folder 516)
    Martin extended his stay a second year. Includes images of 1996 Thanksgiving with exchange teachers; Returned Teachers Conference, October 1998; Martin with Margot Landsman and others, May 1999; etc.
  - American Teachers - Maslowski, David (1996-1997), 1996-2003 (Box 57, Folder 517)
    See also file for Patricia Maslowski.
  - American Teachers - Maslowski, Patricia A. (1996-1997), 1996-2014; Still Images: 4 3x5 color prints (Box 57, Folder 518)
    See also file for David Maslowski. Includes 4 images of Maslowskis and teachers in Hohhut, September 1996.
  - American Teachers - Mason, Nia (1998-2000), 1998-2007; Still Images: 3 3x5 color prints (Box 57, Folder 519-520)
    Includes 3 snapshots of Mason and students in China. Mason stayed on for a second year.
  - American Teachers - McAfee, Bethany Anne (2013-2014) (Box 57, Folder 521)
  - American Teachers - McArdle, Hal (2000-2002), 2000-2006; Still Images: ca. 22 color prints (3x5 - 4x6) (Box 58, Folder 522)
    McArdle extended his stay for a second year. Includes images of school, students, teachers, Nyree Dixon, travel.
  - American Teachers - McDermott, Ben (2010-2011) (Box 58, Folder 523)
  - Menscher, Scott (2000-2001), 2000-2006; Still Images: 3 color prints (3x5 - 4x6) (Box 58, Folder 524)
  - American Teachers - Miles, June Adele (2006-2007), 2005-2010 (Box 58, Folder 525)
  - American Teachers - Molitor, Dennis (1998-1999), 1998-2003 (Box 58, Folder 526)
  - American Teachers - Mullin, Larry (2012-2013) (Box 58, Folder 527)
    Includes headshot photo.
  - American Teachers - Munoz, Billie (2012-2013) (Box 58, Folder 528)
  - American Teachers - O'Donnell, David (2010-2011), 2010-2014 (Box 58, Folder 529)
  - American Teachers - O'Leary, Celine (2012-2013) (Box 58, Folder 530)
    Includes headshot photos.
  - American Teachers - Osborn, Krista (1998-1999), Still Images: 3x5 color prints (Box 58, Folder 531-532)
    Note: some email correspondence is misdated (1995-1996, instead of 1998-1999). Includes snapshots of her students, fellow exchange teachers, travels.
  - American Teachers - Overmeyer, Mark (1998-1999), 1998-2004; Still Images: 3x5 - 4x6 color prints (Box 58, Folder 533)
    Includes snapshots with Dennis Molitor and other exchange teachers and students.
  - American Teachers - Owaroff Snow, Michele (1996-1997), 1996-2004 (Box 58, Folder 534)
  - American Teachers - Page, Susan (2013-2014) (Box 59, Folder 535)
  - American Teachers - Parker, Todd (1997-1998), 1997-2004 (Box 59, Folder 536)
  - American Teachers - Parkhouse, Joanne (1999-2000, 2001-2002), 1999-2009 (Box 59, Folder 537-538)
  - American Teachers - Pedane, David (2006-2007) (Box 59, Folder 539)
  - American Teachers - Perelson, Ira (2003-2004) (Box 59, Folder 540)
  - American Teachers - Perozo, Marcia (2006-2007), 2006-2009 (Box 59, Folder 541)
    Marcia's husband Ciro Petrozo also participated in the exchange program.
  - American Teachers - Perraud, Cecile (2007-2008) (Box 59, Folder 542)
  - American Teachers - Petrilak, Suzanne (1996-1997), 1996-2009; Still Image: 1 3x5 color print (Box 59, Folder 543)
  - American Teachers - Powell, Sandra (1999-2000), 1999-2004 (Box 59, Folder 544)
  - American Teachers - Regan, John M. (Jack) (2001-2002, 2003-2004, 2005-2006), 2001-2012; Still Images: approx. 77 color 4x6 prints (Box 59, Folder 545-546)
    Includes snapshots of exchange teachers, students, holidays; Joanne Parkhouse wedding celebration.
  - American Teachers - Regan, John M. (Jack) (2001-2002, 2003-2004, 2005-2006) (Cards), 2001-2010; Still Images: color 4x6 prints (Box 60, Folder 547-548)
    Notes and letters to Margot Landman, some with enclosed clippings or photos.
  - American Teachers - Reyes, Timothy (2001-2002), 2001-2005 (Box 60, Folder 549)
  - American Teachers - Robbins, A. Douglas (2003-2004), 2003-2012 (Box 60, Folder 550)
  - American Teachers - Rolle, James (2004-2005), 2004-2010 (Box 60, Folder 551)
  - American Teachers - Sakolsky, Ronald (1999-2000), 1999-2006; Still Images: 10 color prints (3x5, 4x6, 1 panoramic) (Box 60, Folder 552)
    Includes snapshots of students, teachers, Mayor's banquet, Tibet
  - American Teachers - Sandvick, Thomas (1998-1999), 1998-2004 (Box 60, Folder 553)
  - American Teachers - Sanford, Richard A. (1997-1998), 1997-2011; Still Images: 14 color prints (3x5, one 4x6). (Box 60, Folder 554-555)
    Includes snapshots of Sanford in China with students and teachers; Chinese exchange teachers in NY, 2001.
  - American Teachers - Schoor, Janet (1997-1998, 2001-2002), 1997-2009; Still Images: 6 color 4x6 prints (Box 61, Folder 556-557)
    Includes snapshots with friends and students, and of clown lesson and party.
  - American Teachers - Serrano, Enid (2001-2002), Still Images: 2 color 4x6 prints (Box 61, Folder 558)
    Includes 2 images of Serrano in China.
  - American Teachers - Shanks, John (2004-2005) (Box 61, Folder 559)
  - American Teachers - Sisisky, Clare, and Zachary Sisisky (2009-2010), 2008-2011 (Box 61, Folder 560)
  - American Teachers - Somerville, Mary Ellen (2000-2001), 2000-2004 (Box 61, Folder 561)
  - American Teachers - Spaier, Michael, and Martha (Martie) Spaier (2000-2001), 2000-2004; Still Images: 3 color 3x5 prints (Box 61, Folder 562)
    Includes images of Spaiers in Holloween costumes and with water buffalo.
  - American Teachers - Strombek, Terry (2007-2008) (Box 61, Folder 563)
  - American Teachers - Tetu, Jean-Jacques, and Katherine Tetu (2010-2011) (Box 61, Folder 564)
  - American Teachers - Tolkoff, Ann Connolly (2000-2001), 2000-2006; Still Images: 4 color prints (3x5 -4x6) (Box 61, Folder 565)
    Includes snapshots of Ann with her classes and students.
  - American Teachers - Vaillancourt, Kimberly (1997-1998), 1997-2004 (Box 61, Folder 566)
  - American Teachers - Wahnquist, Janet F. (1999-2000), 1999-2004 (Box 61, Folder 567)
    Janet's husband, Harvey Wahnquist, accompanied her to China.
  - American Teachers - Walderhaug, Christine (2006-2007), 2005-2009 (Box 61, Folder 568)
    Walderhaug submitted an application and references for 2005-2006, but went to China in 2006-2007.
  - American Teachers - Watson, Tobias (1998-1999), 1998-2006; Still Images: 3 color 4x6 prints (Box 62, Folder 569)
    Includes correspondence from Nancy Watson, who joined her husband in China, and 3 snapshots of them.
  - American Teachers - Wolf, Gerald Bernard (1998-2000), 1998-2004; Still Images: ca. 19 color 3x5 prints (Box 62, Folder 570)
    Wolf's family accompanied him to China. They continued their stay for a second year. Includes images of Wolf and family in China and with students.
  - American Teachers - Wrolson, Karen (2007-2008) (Box 62, Folder 571)
  - American Teachers - Zimmerman, Martha J. (1996-1997), 1996-2008; Still Images: 15 color 3x5 prints (Box 62, Folder 572-573)
    Includes photos of students and and Zimmerman with Chinese colleagues, birthday party.
  - American Teachers - Zinder, Frances (2012-2014), Still Image: 1 color 2x2 print. (Box 62, Folder 574)
    Includes headshot photo. Zinder extended her stay to 2013-2014.
  - American Teachers - Zinn, Eric (2000-2001), 2000-2004 (Box 62, Folder 575)
    Zinn's wife Andrea accompanied him to China.
  - American Teachers (A - Be) - Restricted Material (Box 63, Folder 576)
    Restricted - confidential material
    Confidential material removed from Boxes 50 - 51, folders 450 - 460, for individual teachers: Amper, Angell, Ba, Baboomian, Bachman, Badgley, Barry, Becker, Bergeson.
  - American Teachers (Bi - Bu) - Restricted Material (Box 63, Folder 577)
    Confidential material removed from Boxes 52 - 53, folders 462 - 472, for individual teachers: Bianco, Bronski, Bruss, Burbank, Burnett, Burress, Bush.
  - American Teachers (Ca - Co) - Restricted Material (Box 63, Folder 578)
    Confidential material removed from Box 53, folders 473 - 482, for individual teachers: Castle, Cesario, Chou, Clay, Clower, Cohen, Colletti, Courtice Hart.
  - American Teachers (Cr - D) - Restricted Material (Box 63, Folder 579)
    Confidential material removed from Box 54, folders 483 - 491, for individual teachers: Crispe, Crotchett, Dabney, Davidson, De Yoe, Dixon, Dyro, Dyson.
  - American Teachers (E - G) - Restricted Material (Box 63, Folder 580)
    Confidential material removed from Box 55, folders 492 - 500, for individual teachers: Elliott, Escobar Pocaterra, Fazzolara, Fox, Fray, Frontiera (and Engler), Garcia, Gouck.
  - American Teachers (H - K) - Restricted Material (Box 63, Folder 581)
    Confidential material removed from Boxes 55 - 56. folders 501 - 509, for individual teachers: Happel, Harmeling, Horrigan, James, Jackson (Turley), Joseph, Kelly, Krueger.
  - American Teachers (L - Mc) - Restricted Material (Box 64, Folder 582)
    Confidential material removed from Boxes 56 - 58, folders 512 - 523 for individual teachers: Levin, Lindberg, Maddison, Magboo, Martin, Maslowski (David and Patricia), Mason, McAfee, McArdle.
  - American Teachers (Me - O) - Restricted Material (Box 64, Folder 583)
    Confidential material removed from Box 58, folders 524 - 534, for individual teachers: Menscher, Miles, Molitor, Mullin, Munoz, O'Donnell, O'Leary, Osborn, Overmeyer, Owaroff Snow.
  - American Teachers (P - R) - Restricted Material (Box 64, Folder 584)
    Confidential material removed from Boxes 59-60, folders 535 - 551, for individual teachers: Page, Parker, Parkhouse, Pedane, Perelson, Perozo, Perraud, Petrilak, Powell, Regan, Reyes, Robbins, Rolle
  - American Teachers (S) - Restricted Material (Box 64, Folder 585)
    Confidential material removed from Boxes 60 - 61, folders 552 - 563, for individual teachers: Sakolsky, Sandvick, Sanford, Schoor, Serrano, Shanks, Sisisky (Clare and Zachary), Somerville, Spaier (Michael and Martha), Strombeck.
  - American Teachers (T - V) - Restricted Material (Box 64, Folder 586)
    Confidential material removed from Box 61, folders 564 - 566, for individual teachers: Tetu (Jean-Jacques and Katherine), Tolkoff, Vaillancourt.
  - American Teachers (W - Z) - Restricted Material (Box 64, Folder 587)
    Confidential material removed from Box 62, folders 567 - 575, for individual teachers: Wahnquist, Walderhaug, Watson, Wolf, Wrolson, Zimmerman, Zinder, Zinn.
  - Teachers Exchange Program (TEP) Reference Files - Jeanne Phillips, 1998-2003 (Box 65, Folder 588)
    Reports from China. File includes manuscript of article, In Memory of Ms. Renee Kwang-Ming Nieh, by Clyde Tsung-Kong Nieh.
  - Teachers Exchange Program (TEP) Reference Files - City Guides (U .S.), 2000-2009 (Box 65, Folder 589)
    Guides based on experiences of Chinese exchange teachers.
  - Teachers Exchange Program (TEP) Reference Files - City Guides (China), 1998-2007 (Box 65, Folder 590)
    Guides based on experiences of American exchange teachers.
  - Teachers Exchange Program (TEP) Reference Files - Annotated Bibliography on China, 1996-2001 (Box 65, Folder 591)
    Annotated reading lists prepared by Margot Landman.
  - Teachers Exchange Program (TEP) Reference Files - Application Forms for American Teachers, 1999-2004; 2012 (Box 65, Folder 592)
    Sample application packets (blank).
  - Teachers Exchange Program (TEP) Reference Files - Forms for China (Instructions), 2001; undated (Box 65, Folder 593)
    Forms and information for teachers heading to China. Includes PRC "Physical Examination Form for Foreigner."
  - Teachers Exchange Program (TEP) Reference Files - Chinese Textbooks Order Forms, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 594)
    Recommended textbooks for Chinese language learning.
  - Teachers Exchange Program (TEP) Reference Files - "Reverse Culture Shock", 1999-2005 (Box 65, Folder 595)
    Includes returned teachers' 1999 responses on the subject.
  - American Schools - Bangor Public Schools (ME), 2001-2003 (Box 65, Folder 596)
  - American Schools - Beacon School, 1997-2006 (Box 65, Folder 597)
  - American Schools - Beebe Elementary School (Melrose, MA), 1997-1999 (Box 65, Folder 598)
  - American Schools - Belmont Public Schools (MA), 1997-2006 (Box 65, Folder 599)
  - American Schools - Bishop Kelley High School (Tulsa), 2007-2010 (Box 65, Folder 600)
  - American Schools - Boston Public Schools, 1997-2008 (Box 66, Folder 601)
  - American Schools - Boulder Valley Public Schools (CO), 1996-1997 (Box 66, Folder 602)
  - American Schools - Brockton Public Schools (MA), 2005-2010 (Box 66, Folder 603)
  - American Schools - Broken Arrow Senior High School (OK), 2006 (Box 66, Folder 604)
  - American Schools - Brookline High School (MA), 1996-2007 (Box 66, Folder 605)
  - American Schools - Cambridge Rindge and Latin School, 1996-2002 (Box 66, Folder 606)
  - American Schools - Cascia Hall Preparatory School (Tulsa), 2007-2008 (Box 66, Folder 607)
  - American Schools - Cherry Creek Middle School (Denver), 1996-2003 (Box 66, Folder 608)
  - American Schools - Collegiate School (New York), 1998-2001; Still Image: 1 color 4x6 print (Box 66, Folder 609)
    Includes one image of students at dinner.
  - American Schools - Douglas County School District (CO), 2006 (Box 66, Folder 610)
  - American Schools - Edgewood School (New Haven), 2012 (Box 66, Folder 611)
  - American Schools - Fort Gibson Public Schools (OK), 2008-2012 (Box 66, Folder 612)
  - American Schools - Henniker Community School (NH), 2003-2011 (Box 66, Folder 613)
  - American Schools - Holland Hall School (Tulsa), 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 614)
  - American Schools - Kearsarge Regional High School (NH), 1997-2008 (Box 66, Folder 615)
  - American Schools - School District of La Crosse (WI), 1997-2008 (Box 66, Folder 616-617)
  - American Schools - Lee's Summit R-7 School District (MO), 2008 (Box 67, Folder 618)
  - American Schools - Lexington High School (MA), 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 619)
  - American Schools - Longmeadow Public Schools (MA), 1997-1999 (Box 67, Folder 620)
  - American Schools - Milton Public Schools (MA), 2003 (Box 67, Folder 621)
  - American Schools - Milwaukee Public Schools, 1996-2012 (Box 67, Folder 622-623)
  - American Schools - Newton Public Schools (MA), 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 624)
    Includes correspondence and materials from The China Exchange Initiative handbooks.
  - American Schools - New York City Board of Education, 1997-2003 (Box 67, Folder 625)
  - American Schools - District 13 (Brooklyn), 1999-2006; Still Images: 7 color 3x5 prints (Box 67, Folder 626)
    Includes photos of 1999 Welcome Reception for visiting teachers from China.
  - American Schools - District 25 (Flushing, Queens), 1996-2000 (Box 67, Folder 627)
    Includes brochures for visits of the Chinese Education Delegation to New York City, May 1995, and the New York City Education Delegation to China, April 1998.
  - American Schools - District 29 (Rosedale, Queens), 2000-2003 (Box 67, Folder 628)
  - American Schools - East-West School of International Studies (Queens), 2005-2007 (Box 67, Folder 629)
  - American Schools - Edward R. Murrow High School (Brooklyn), 2000 (Box 67, Folder 630)
  - American Schools - Garden School (Queens), 2001-2007 (Box 67, Folder 631)
  - American Schools - Grover Cleveland High School (Queens), 1997; 2003 (Box 67, Folder 632)
  - American Schools - International High School at LaGuardia Community College (Queens), 1997; 2000; 2004 (Box 67, Folder 633)
  - American Schools - John Bowne High School (Flushing, Queens), 1999-2000 (Box 67, Folder 634)
  - American Schools - Legacy High School (New York), 2001-2002 (Box 67, Folder 635)
  - American Schools - Lower East Side Preparatory High School (New York), 1998-1999 (Box 67, Folder 636)
  - American Schools - Morris High School (The Bronx), 1997 (Box 67, Folder 637)
  - American Schools - Science Skills Center High School (Brooklyn), 1996-2001 (Box 67, Folder 638)
  - American Schools - Tottenville High School (Staten Island), 1997; 2001 (Box 68, Folder 639)
  - American Schools - Norman Public Schools (OK), 2006-2012 (Box 68, Folder 640)
  - American Schools - Owasso High School (OK), 2010-2012 (Box 68, Folder 641)
  - American Schools - Poudre School District (Fort Collins, CO), 1996-2004 (Box 68, Folder 642)
  - American Schools - Plum Borough School District (PA), 2000 (Box 68, Folder 643)
  - American Schools - Ponca City Public Schools (OK), 2010-2011 (Box 68, Folder 644)
  - American Schools - P.S. 163 (Manhattan), 1998-1999; 2003 (Box 68, Folder 645)
  - American Schools - Portland Public Schools (OR), 2001-2005 (Box 68, Folder 646)
  - American Schools - Quabbin Regional School District (MA), 1997-1998 (Box 68, Folder 647)
  - American Schools - Quincy Upper School (Boston), 2001-2008 (Box 68, Folder 648)
  - American Schools - Royal Oak School District (MI), 2007-2008 (Box 68, Folder 649)
  - American Schools - Saint Edward's School (Vero Beach, FL), 2003-2012 (Box 68, Folder 650)
  - American Schools - Sandwich Public Schools (MA), 1998; Still Image: 1 color 8x10 print (Box 68, Folder 651)
    Includes group photo of staff.
  - American Schools - Shady Hill School (Cambridge, MA), 2005-2006 (Box 68, Folder 652)
  - American Schools - Snowden International School (Boston), 1997-2010 (Box 68, Folder 653)
  - American Schools - Southampton Public Schools (NY), 2002-2005 (Box 68, Folder 654)
  - American Schools - Stamford Public Schools (CT), 2004-2007 (Box 68, Folder 655)
  - American Schools - Tulsa Public Schools (OK), 2003-2012 (Box 68, Folder 656)
  - American Schools - Westport Public Schools (CT), 1996-2010 (Box 68, Folder 657)
  - American Schools - Whitman-Hanson Regional School District (MA), 2007-2011 (Box 68, Folder 658)
  - Oversized Material (Box 69)
    Separated oversized material. From Box 45, folder 365: Suzhou No. 1 Middle School, Newspaper publication (in Chinese), 2001 (2 issues and undated section). From Box 45, folder 370: Yang Zhou Ri Bao newspaper, 2001-11-5, 8 pages (Yangzhou Schools). From Box 51, folder 460, 2 photos (7.75 x 12 - 9 x 12 color prints) of Roy Bergeson meeting with Chinese school administrators, circa December 2000.
- Board of Directors, Committees, and Members records, 1958, 1965-2014; 11
  Board materials
  The Board of Directors, Committees, and Members series in RG 8 contains bound Minutes books from 1966 through 2007. (For later Board records, up to 2014, see RG 7, FA1189.) Inactive Members files – arranged in a few alphabetical sets – constitute the remainder of the series. Files are variously labeled Deceased Members or Former Members, but the labels were not consistently applied and the Former Members encompass many who are deceased. While there is a good deal of routine material in the members files – form letters and acknowledgements – some of the early files include personal correspondence concerning the organization and its program directions.
  - Minutes Book, Volumes 1 - 2, 1966 September - 1969 November (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    Volume 1: 1966 September 9 - 1968 April 25; Volume 2: 1968 June 3 - 1969 November 2.
  - Minutes Book, Volumes 3 - 4, 1970 January - 1973 May (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    Volume 3: 1970 January 26 - 1972 February 1; Volume 4: 1972 May 4 - 1973 May 16.
  - Minutes Book, Volumes 5 - 6, 1973 October - 1976 October (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
    Volume 5: 1973 October 29 - 1974 November 4; Volume 6: 1975 January 24 - 1976 October 7.
  - Minutes Book, Volumes 7 - 8, 1977 February - 1987 April (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
    Volume 7: 1977 February 4 - 1982 May 20; Volume 8: 1982 December 13 - 1987 April 6.
  - Minutes Book, Volumes 9 - 10, 1987 December - 1996 March (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
    Volume 9: 1987 December 10 - 1991 September 27; Volume 10: 1992 October 22 - 1996 March 13.
  - Minutes Book, Volumes 11 - 12, 1996 July 12 - 2007 November 8 (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
    Some of the Minutes are filed out of order. Volume 12 includes Minutes of Executive Committee meeting, June 20, 2000, but otherwise begins with the December 7, 2001, Board meeting.
  - Former Members Files: Resigned, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (A) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (B) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (C-D) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (E-F) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Eckstein, Alexander), 1966-1979 (Box 7, Folder 18-19)
    Includes portrait photo, circa 1972
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Fairbanks, John King), 1966-1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (G) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Gilmore, Robert W.), 1966-1988 (Box 8, Folder 22-23)
    Includes portrait photo by Fabian Bachrach.
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Gomperts, Jack), 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (H-J), Still Image (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Hammer, Armand), 1982-1990; Still Image (Box 8, Folder 26)